{
  "585": {"1":{"question": "Johnny Depp", "exp": "portrayed", "option_1": "Jack Sparrow", "option_2": "Davy Jones", "right": "Jack Sparrow", "subj": "Pop", "author": "Bayou TriviaLinked fans - thanks for your endless love and support."},"2":{"question": "Jack Sparrow", "exp": "is central to the film series Pirates of the", "option_1": "Ionian", "option_2": "Caribbean", "right": "Caribbean", "subj": "Leisure"},"3":{"question": "Caribbean", "exp": "is home to the nation of", "option_1": "Dominica", "option_2": "Easter Island", "right": "Dominica", "subj": "Geography"},"4":{"question": "Dominica", "exp": "has its capital at", "option_1": "Roseau", "option_2": "Bridgetown", "right": "Roseau", "subj": "Geography"},"5":{"question": "Roseau", "exp": "is known for its roots in the world of", "option_1": "Constanza", "option_2": "Creole", "right": "Creole", "subj": "History"},"6":{"question": "Creole", "exp": "dish:", "option_1": "Gumpy", "option_2": "Gumbo", "right": "Gumbo", "subj": "Leisure"},"7":{"question": "Gumbo", "exp": "is the official state cuisine of", "option_1": "Louisiana", "option_2": "Indiana", "right": "Louisiana", "subj": "Geography"},"8":{"question": "Louisiana", "exp": "recently legalized the sport of", "option_1": "Noodling", "option_2": "Terramenting", "right": "Noodling", "subj": "Sports"},"9":{"question": "Noodling", "exp": "involves barehanded-catching of", "option_1": "Crabs", "option_2": "Catfish", "right": "Catfish", "subj": "Sports"},"10":{"question": "Catfish", "exp": "is a term also used to describe a", "option_1": "Fake Profile", "option_2": "Fake SAT Score", "right": "Fake Profile", "subj": "Leisure"},"11":{"question": "Fake Profile", "exp": "might be found on", "option_1": "Twitter", "option_2": "TSA Pre-Check", "right": "Twitter", "subj": "Business"},"12":{"question": "Twitter", "exp": "was co-founded by", "option_1": "Jack Dorsey", "option_2": "Emmett Shear", "right": "Jack Dorsey", "subj": "Business"}},
  "586": {"1":{"question": "Trees", "exp": "are where you might find an", "option_1": "Apple", "option_2": "Onion", "right": "Apple", "subj": "STEM", "author": "Thank you Brandon Lee for writing today's path ~"},"2":{"question": "Apple", "exp": "is a company based in", "option_1": "Oregon", "option_2": "California", "right": "California", "subj": "Business"},"3":{"question": "California", "exp": "is the birthplace of author John", "option_1": "Steinbeck", "option_2": "Orwell", "right": "Steinbeck", "subj": "Literature"},"4":{"question": "Steinbeck", "exp": "authored", "option_1": "East of Eden", "option_2": "Westworld", "right": "East of Eden", "subj": "Literature"},"5":{"question": "East of Eden", "exp": "is loosely based on the biblical figure", "option_1": "Cain", "option_2": "Davy", "right": "Cain", "subj": "Literature"},"6":{"question": "Cain", "exp": "is pronounced the same as", "option_1": "Cane", "option_2": "Dantileo", "right": "Cane", "subj": "Language"},"7":{"question": "Cane", "exp": "is a species of grass used for the production of", "option_1": "Salt", "option_2": "Sugar", "right": "Sugar", "subj": "STEM"},"8":{"question": "Sugar", "exp": "in a band name precedes", "option_1": "Balkristo", "option_2": "Ray", "right": "Ray", "subj": "Music"},"9":{"question": "Ray", "exp": "is the first name of author", "option_1": "Bradbury", "option_2": "Williamtorris", "right": "Bradbury", "subj": "Literature"},"10":{"question": "Bradbury", "exp": "wrote the book", "option_1": "Celsius 139", "option_2": "Fahrenheit 451", "right": "Fahrenheit 451", "subj": "Literature"},"11":{"question": "Fahrenheit 451", "exp": "is the temperature at which this material burns:", "option_1": "Ornament", "option_2": "Paper", "right": "Paper", "subj": "STEM"},"12":{"question": "Paper", "exp": "in a cocktail name precedes the word", "option_1": "Plane", "option_2": "Porintis", "right": "Plane", "subj": "Leisure"}},
  "587": {"1":{"question": "Riyadh", "exp": "is about 420 km away from the", "option_1": "Persian Gulf", "option_2": "Sea of Azov", "right": "Persian Gulf", "subj": "Geography", "author": "Fun fact: Citizen Kane is every film snob's favorite film!"},"2":{"question": "Persian Gulf", "exp": "can be accessed from the Gulf of Oman via the", "option_1": "Strait of Molucca", "option_2": "Strait of Hormuz", "right": "Strait of Hormuz", "subj": "Geography"},"3":{"question": "Strait of Hormuz", "exp": "was once conquered by", "option_1": "Portugal", "option_2": "Norway", "right": "Portugal", "subj": "History"},"4":{"question": "Portugal", "exp": "has a national dish known as", "option_1": "Haddock", "option_2": "Cod", "right": "Cod", "subj": "Leisure"},"5":{"question": "Cod", "exp": "is also an acronym for the popular video game franchise", "option_1": "Call of Duty", "option_2": "Call of DeLano", "right": "Call of Duty", "subj": "Business"},"6":{"question": "Call of Duty", "exp": "is published by", "option_1": "Activision", "option_2": "Warner Bros.", "right": "Activision", "subj": "Business"},"7":{"question": "Activision", "exp": "was purchased, in 2022, by the tech giant", "option_1": "Apple", "option_2": "Microsoft", "right": "Microsoft", "subj": "Business"},"8":{"question": "Microsoft", "exp": "was co-founded by Paul Allen and", "option_1": "Bill Gates", "option_2": "Steve Jobs", "right": "Bill Gates", "subj": "Business"},"9":{"question": "Bill Gates", "exp": "owns a large estate in Bellevue, WA nicknamed the 2.0 version of", "option_1": "Xanadu", "option_2": "Delphi", "right": "Xanadu", "subj": "Business"},"10":{"question": "Xanadu", "exp": "is the fictional estate of the powerful, wealthy, and lonely Charles Kane, the subject of Orson Welles' 1941 film", "option_1": "Citizen Kane", "option_2": "It's a Wonderful Life", "right": "Citizen Kane", "subj": "History"},"11":{"question": "Citizen Kane", "exp": "speaks the famous final words,", "option_1": "Rosebud", "option_2": "Rosemary", "right": "Rosebud", "subj": "History"},"12":{"question": "Rosebud", "exp": "reservation is a Sioux reservation in", "option_1": "South Carolina", "option_2": "South Dakota", "right": "South Dakota", "subj": "History"}}

 }
